<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:paddingBottom="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    android:paddingLeft="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingRight="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingTop="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    app:layout_behavior="@string/appbar_scrolling_view_behavior"
    tools:context="com.example.mdaij.ccc.About"
    tools:showIn="@layout/activity_about">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">
    <android.support.v7.widget.CardView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:elevation="4dp"
        android:id="@+id/view2">

        <TextView
            android:padding="5dp"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium"
            android:text="Wrap up your mind as we introduce the new Code Club from CBIT. Starting from today, we will be rolling out a fresh experience of collaborative projects, events, workshops and much more.
What is CBIT Code Club?
CBIT Code Club aims at informing students about technical events happening in our college, providing online tutorials along with a certificate and giving a platform for members to work on collaborative projects.
Why CBIT Code Club?
Have an idea for your project? Great! But a mere idea would not work if you cant take your project any further. Code Club endeavors to support this idea by creating a platform for members to share their projects with other members. In effect, you can get your projects done by building a team. And the opposite is also true. You can always help others build their projects.
Programming is an incredible skill that engages both creative and problem-solving skills. Code club teaches much more than programming a computer and much more than being a developer. It lets you interact with other people making the club projects fun and creative and helping students understand how to solve problems in an easier way.
Who can join?
Any enthusiast can join!
So why waste time? Get involved! It’s all about your commitment!⁠⁠⁠⁠"
            android:id="@+id/textView3"
            android:layout_alignBottom="@+id/view2"
            android:layout_centerHorizontal="true" />

    </android.support.v7.widget.CardView>
    </ScrollView>


</RelativeLayout>
